<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
  <collection slug="silverhorn">
    <metadata>
      <category>American Indian Art</category>
      <artist>Silver Horn (Haungooah), North American Indian, 1860-1940</artist>
      <media>One of 75 drawings contained within a bound book; graphite and colored pencil on paper</media>
      <dimensions>Overall: 11 3/4 x 14 3/4 in. (29.845 x 37.465 cm)</dimensions>
      <provenance>Gift of Mr. and Mrs. Dudley C. Brown</provenance>
      <gallerylocation>208</gallerylocation>
      <thumbnail>img/silverhorn/silverhorn-7.jpg</thumbnail>
    </metadata>
    <images directory="img/silverhorn/">
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-1.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          White Horse, Kiowa Killing Pawnee, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-2.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Ka-nati, Kiowa Killing Pawnee, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-3.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Clandestine Meeting Betwwen Ke-ah-bone (Kiowa) and the Wife of Pan quodle (Kiowa) at Pan quodle's Tent who he Drug Inside Unconscious, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-4.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Mau-hin (Kiowa) Killing Pawnee, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-5.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Broken Wrist (Kiowa) and Cheyenne Fighting: Broken Wrist on Right, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-6.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Taw-ate, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-7.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Big Brown (Kiowa) and Five of His Braves Dancing - Making Medicine Preparatory to a Buffalo Hunt, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-8.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          As-on-daugh (Kiowa) Stealing Quodle-qeah mah (Kiowa Maiden), as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-9.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Big Bow Killing Calvary Officer and Private, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-10.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Big Bow Killing Calvary Officer and Private, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-11.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Medicine Lodge, Kiowa, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-12.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Cauder-daugh (Kiowa) Stealing Kiowa Woman, Cauder-zone, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-13.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Making Foundation for Kiowa Medicine Woman, Cauder-zone, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-14.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          To-hane-daugh and Party Carrying "Medicine" to Medicine Lodge, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-15.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          I-yant and Young Men Dancing, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-16.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Kiowa Lodges--Encampment, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-17.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Tine-tah and Young Man Dressed to Represent Buffaloes, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-18.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          While Hunting Them to Procure a Buffalo Bull's Head for a Medicine Dance, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-19.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Haun-geah-ah Ka (Kiowa) is Surprised by Navajo while Upia Tru (sic?) Trying to to Rob a Buzzard's Nest. Navajo upon Seeing Haun-geah-ah Ka Attempts to Kill him but is Killed Himself by Huan-geah-ah Kah's Friend Dane-Cah (Kiowa) who upon seeing the Navajo , 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-20.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          To-yape (Kiowa) Killing Ute with Gun, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-21.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Wo-e-boy (Kiowa) Stealing Mo-quo Kiowa Girl, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-22.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Hoaf-to-ti (Kiowa) and Two Braves Dancing War Dance, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-23.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Koy-mau Making Medicine for Devine Blessing, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-24.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Audle-ta Returning with His Wife after Capturing Her from Tane-die with whom She Eloped, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-25.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          On-ta-zoodli (Kiowa) Stealing Choue-geat (Kiowa), as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-26.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Chanate (Kiowa) Stealing Two Maidens (Kiowa), as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-27.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          White Horse (Kiowa) and Two of His Braves Dancing, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-28.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Pau-geat and To-ya (Kiowas) Making Love to Two Kiowa Maidens, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-29.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Chane-doodle (Kiowa) Overtaken After Eloping with the Wife of Tau-dome, Tau-dome Killed His Wife and Takes All of Chane-doodle's Clothing and Ponies, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-30.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Ko-mo-beadle Stealing Cheyenne Woman, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-31.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Au-yea and Wife out Hunting, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-32.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Cheyenne Killing To-ya-so (Kiowa), as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-33.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Tong-ke-i-he (Kiowa) Killing Pawnee, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-34.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Pau-ah (Kiowa) Killing Two Pawnees, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-35.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Kiowa Woman Dancing, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-36.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Bau-ah (Kiowa) Killing Pawnee, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-37.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Pawnees Returning to Their Homes After Losing Their Ponies in Engagements with Kiowas, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-38.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          An-one (Kiowa) Being Killed by Cheyenne, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-39.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Kiowa Lodges, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-40.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Pe-ah (Kiowa) Stealing Da-him's Wife from His Lodge, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-41.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Do-yant Eloping with Kiowa Maiden, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-42.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Pawnees and Kiowas Fight in Circle made of Brush after Repulsing U.S. Calvary, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-43.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Mo-chi (Kiowa) Stealing Kan-quodle quodle (Kiowa) Maiden, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-44.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          White Horse Killing Ute, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-45.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Cheyenne Women Dancing, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-46.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Cheyenne Braves Dancing, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-47.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Bau-daugh Killing Infantry Officer, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-48.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Navajo Returning to His Tepee and Finds Tracks of His Horses that have been Stolen by Kiowas - Pursues Kiowas who are just over the Hill from His Camp and is Killed by Them, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-49.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Tah-bah (Kiowa) Kills Eagle Perched on Tree Top but Fails to See Three Deer Grazing Near Trunk of Tree until after He Shoots When the Deer Escape, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-50.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Kaw-him (Kiowa) Wounds Deer and Pursues Until He Overtakes it when He Kills It, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-51.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Paudlety (Kiowa) Steals Kiowa Maiden, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-52.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Tso-tigh and Two Braves Dancing War Dance, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-53.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Go-ye tahbo (Kiowa) Fails in His Attempt to Persuade Kiowa Married Woman to Elope with Him, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-54.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Cheyenne Killing Ah-go (Kiowa), as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-55.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Cheyenne Killing Ute, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-56.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Cheyenne Killing Quodle pah (Kiowa), as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-57.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Ah-tah-lah (Kiowa) Journeying to His Sweetheart's Lodge, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-58.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Tau-ta-Kah (Kiowa) Making Medicine in Accordance with Old Custom, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-59.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Lu-hah (Kiowa) Going into Medicine Lodge to Make "Medicine" for Departing Officers Just Preparing to Leave, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-60.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Tone-go (Kiowa) Meeting His Sweetheart, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-61.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Kiowa Woke-on-Lodge. Ah-done-da-ga at Entrance Receiving Food from Taw mah (Kiowa) Woman After Night's Debautch, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-62.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Mauu-geah (Kiowa) Killing Sioux, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-63.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Zabile (Kiowa) Steals Kiowa Maiden who afterwards becomes his wife, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-64.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Pautigh and Braves Performing Tribal Dance, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-65.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Braves Dancing around White Captive Who is being Burnt to the Stake (After being Scalped), as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-66.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          I-Yau (Kiowa) Kills one of the Sioux Attacking Him and then Escapes, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-67.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Haun-pa (Kiowa) Making Love to Bo-in- cha's Wife at the Utes' Camp at Night, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-68.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Cheyenne Kills Chane-tone (Kiowa), as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-69.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Peadle-Kah and Mau-Saw (Kiowas) Rivals for the Affections of Kiowa Maiden - Peadle-Kah Successful, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-70.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Zabile (Kiowa) Steals Kiowa Maiden who Afterwards becomes His Wife, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-71.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Quauah, Head Commanche Chief Making Medicine Before Engaging in Wo-gau Debautch, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-72.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Sau-taugh-Koy Steals Guo-geiu-ha's Wife at the Ute's Camp at Night, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-73.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Guo-chaudle (Kiowa) behind Medicine Shield Beckoning for His Sweetheart to Come to Him, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-74.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Mine-yock (Kiowa) Kills Pawnee, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
      <image>
        <filename>silverhorn-75.jpg</filename>
        <caption>
          Kiowa Performing a Messiah Dance, as captioned by D. P. Brown, 1883
        </caption>
      </image>
    </images>
  </collection>
</data>
